樂隊注意  向前齊步走
DRUM MAJOR: Band, forward march!
十秒倒數開始
MAN : Ten count to the VS,
二  一  開始
in two, one... go.
Behati到位了
I got Behati.
Doutzen在這
Doutzen is here.
Adriana還有20秒
Got 20 seconds for Adriana.
Ale在我這
I have Ale with me.
第五個是Alessandra
Five's following Alessandra.
給第七個來個特寫  鏡頭到第七個
Seven, close-up-- let me go to seven.
她轉身時給個特寫
Give me a close-up when she turns.
-漂亮  -Lindsay  倒數第三位  第十個
Beautiful. Lindsay, ten of 12.
-Lily到了  -這就來
Lily's in the house. There she goes.
Elsa開始走台
Elsa is walking.
Karlie在這  Karlie候場
Here comes Karlie. Stand by, Karlie.
-Candice出場  -這可是價值千萬的胸罩
Go, Candice! That's the $10 million bra.
讓她上場  讓她走  快點
Let her go, let her go, let her go!
我好緊張啊
I'm nervous!
後台誰負責首飾
Who's doing the jewelry back here?!
準備讓Taylor Swift從左側登台
Stand by to send Taylor Swift from stage left.
她來了
She's coming.
-開始  -第一位準備從六號門入場
Here we go. Stand byfor the first girl on six.
上Fall Out Boy的佈景
Preset Fall Out Boy.
一切就緒  準備開始
We're a-rockin' and we're a-rollin'.
-開始緊張了  -你看上去美極了
Getting nervous. You look amazing!
-看著就身價百萬  -好極了
Looks good for one million! Awesome.
Bahati就在這  她來了  她來了
Bahati's right here. She's made it, she's made it.
A Great Big World準備就緒
A Great Big World in position.
燈光全開
Light shining through! Aah!
Neon Jungle準備好
Stand by, Neon Jungle. Three,, twoone, go!
三  二  一  開始
女士們先生們
ANNOUNCER: Ladies andtl genemen,
掌聲有請Fall Out Boy
please welcome to the stage, Fall Out Boy!
?Whoa, oh
?Whoa, whoa
?B-B-Be careful making wishes in the dark, dark ?
?Can't be sure when they've hit their mark and ?
?Besides in the mean, meantime, I'm just ?
?Dreaming of tearing you apart ?
?I'm in the de-details with the Devil ?
?The world can never get me on my ?
?Level, I just got to ?Get you off the cage,
I'm a young lover's rage ?
?Gonna need a spark to ignite
?My songs know what you did ?In the dark
?So light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up, up, light 'em up, up ?
?I'm on fire, light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up ?
?Im 'on fire ?
?Whoa, oh
?Whoa, whoa
?In the dark, dark
?Whoa, oh
?Whoa, whoa
?In the dark, dark
女士們先生們  有請Taylor Swift
Ladies and gentlemen, Taylor Swift.
?Writers keep writing what they write ?
?Somewhere another pretty vein just died ?
?I've got the scars from tomorrow and I wish ?
?You could see that you're the antidote ?
?To everything except for me
?A constellation of tears on your ?
?Lashes burn everything you love then burn the ?
?Ashes, in the end everything collides, my childhood ?
?Spat back out the monster that you see ?
?My songs know what you did in the ? ?Dark
?So light 'em up, up, up, light 'em ? ?Up, up, up,
light 'em up, up ? 79 00:04: 00:04:08,047
?I'm on fire ?
?Light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up, up, light 'em ?Up, up,
I'm on fire ?
?Whoa, oh
?Whoa, whoa, in the dark, dark ?
?Whoa, oh, whoa, whoa
?In the dark, dark
晚上好  紐約
TAYLOR SWIFT: Oh, good evening, New York City,
歡迎來到《維多利亞的秘密時尚秀》
and welcome to the Victoria's Secret fashion Show.
我是Taylor
My name is Taylor.
他們是我的朋友  Patrick  Pete  Andy和Joe
These are my friends Patrick, Pete, Andy and Joe,
他們是Fall Out Boy  而她們
and they are Fall Out Boy. And these...
是2013年維密天使
are the 2013 Victoria's Secret Angels.
PATRICK STUMP: ?My songs know what you did ?In the dark...
?My songs know
?What you did in the ?Dark...
?So light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up, I'm on fire ?
?Whoa, oh
?Whoa, whoa
?In the dark, dark
?Whoa, oh
?Whoa, whoa
?Light 'em up, up, up ?
?Light 'em up, up, up,
light 'em ? ?Up, up, I'm on fire ?
?Light 'em up ? ?Whoa, oh
?Whoa
?Whoa, oh, whoa
?Whoa.
太棒了
Whoo! Amazing!
讓我們把你領出去化妝做頭髮
Let's move you out and let's do hair and makeup, touchups outside.
細節出去弄
有人看見Kasia了嗎
Does anyone have eyes on Kasia?
Behati在我這
I got Behati.
我們需要Candice到標記處來
We need Candice on this cross.
我看見她了  看見了  沒問題
I got her, I got her. No problem.
很好  Doutzen到了  我們準備好了
Oh, good. Doutzen is here. We're ready for you.
天使們準備就緒
We're good on models.
準備登台
We are standing by.
我覺得我從小到大
LILY ALDRIDGE: I have been walking up and down
就一直在模擬天橋走秀
fake runways my whole life, I think.
我第一次知道時尚秀時
The first time I was introduced to a fashion show,
我好像才四歲
I was, like, four years old.
我的夢想
LINDSAY ELLINGSON: My dream was to walk in
就是參加維密時尚內衣秀
the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show.
對於來自巴西小鎮的我來說
ADRIANA LIMA: Coming from a small town in Brazil,
這太了不起了
it's huge.
我就想成為那些女孩中的一員
ALESSANDRA AMBROSIO: I just wanted to be one of those girls,
加入這個不可思議的大家庭
you know, and wanted to be part of this incredible family.
我18歲時
When I turned 18,
我就定下目標
I had set a goal of being
要參加維密時尚內衣秀
in the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show
卻不知道這意味著什麼
and had no comprehension of what was ahead.
我當時年紀小  缺乏安全感  很害怕
DOUTZEN KROES: I was young and insecure and very scared.
我來維密的第一件事
CANDICE SWANEPOEL: The first thing I did
就是參加時尚內衣秀的模特選拔
with Victoria's Secret was the fashion show casting.
很多人問我們
Hi. MONICA MITRO: A lot of people ask us,
你們選拔都看重什麼
"What do you look for when you're cas?"Ting
對我們來說  最重要的是找到
For us, it's very, very important to have someone
熱情向上  積極開朗的人
who's enthusiastic and always positive and always happy--
我們要找一位美麗健康的女性
this gorgeous, healthy woman.
我從沒這麼緊張過
I had never been more nervous in my entire life.
把果凍和水泥混起來的感覺
If you could mix Jell-O and a cement block together...
-就是當時我腿的感覺  -慢點  慢點
that is how my legs felt. Slow down, slow down.
這是個成為巨星的好機會
This is a real opportunity
to become a big star.
我當時很年輕  對我來說簡直不可思議
I was so young-- it was just mind-blowing for me
我能夠參加走秀  能夠站上天橋
that I'd booked the show and that I was there.
我見到了Heidi  Laetitia  Stephanie
I saw Heidi, I saw Laetitia, I saw Stephanie.
還有Tyra Banks  Gisele  Adriana
Tyra Banks, Gisele, Adriana...
天吶天吶  真不敢相信我居然在這
"Oh, my God, oh, my God. I can't believe I'm here.
她們太美了
They're so beautiful."
I never imagined that I would be on that runway.
我從未想過自己能參與維密內衣秀
?And we're gonna let it burn, burn, burn ?
?Burn, we're gonna let it burn... ?
My first time doing the VS Fashion Show,
第一次加入維密內衣秀
改變了我的模特生涯
that changeden my tire career.
維密能推動你的事業
It definitely puts you in the next level.
提高了我的知名度
BEHATI PRINSLOO: That's what really got me out into
the whole entire world.
大家都知道你是誰
Everybody knows who you are.
It's such an incredible journey.
這是段無與倫比的旅程
歲月如梭
The yearnts we by so fast.
真希望時間能走得慢一點
I wish I could slow down.
我到現在都還沒緩過神來  但我做到了
I still don't know how it happened, but here I am.
我成為了維密天使
I made it.
I'm just one lucky girl.
我成為了維密天使
我是位幸運的女孩
I'm just one lucky girl.
女士們先生們  掌聲歡迎A Great Big World
Ladies and gentleman, please welcome a Great Big World!
?Say something, I'm giving up on you ?
?I'll be the one if you want me to ?
?Anywhere, I would've followed you ?
?Say something
?I'm giving up on you ?
?And I...
?Am feeling so small
?It was over my head
?I know nothing at all
?And I...
?Will stumble and fall
?I'm still learning to love ?
?Just starting to crawl
?Say something
?I'm giving up on you ?
?I'm sorry ?
?That I couldn't get to you ?
?Anywhere I would have followed you ?
?Say something
?I'm giving up on you ?
?And I...
?Will swallow my pride
?You're the one ?
?That I love
?And I'm saying good-bye ?
?Say something
?I'm giving up on you ?
?And I'm sorry ?
?That I couldn't get to you ?
?And anywhere
?I would have followed you
?Oh...
?Say something
?I'm giving up on you ?
?Say something.
Copy that! Nick, go!
收到  Nick快去吧
Release Lily and go help.
讓Lily走  你先去幫忙
-讓天使們過  -"迷海遺艦"馬上開始
Let the girls through.
Going into Shipwreck.
大伙們  翅膀來咯  借過
Okay, guys, wings coming to you, wings coming to you.
I don't know how it feels to be stuck on a deserted island.
我不知道被困在孤島上是什麼感覺
I would love it. I would hate it.
-我一定會喜歡  -我討厭極了
我喜歡沙灘  也喜歡大海
I love the beach. I love the ocean.
要看誰與我同行
It depends who I could bring.
隨便吧  這就行了  對吧
That-That'll do, right?
我會帶著...
I would bring...
手機
my phone.
衝浪板
A surfboard.
燒烤爐
A barbecue.
一把刀
A knife.
一位強壯的男士
A really strong man.
無線網絡不能少
And obviously we need Wi-Fi.
無線網絡
無線網絡不能少
And obviously we need Wi-Fi.
衛星電話
A satellite telephone.
-我的孩子和家人  -水
My kids and my family. A drink.
Should we build a fire?
需要生火嗎
我能鑽木取火  我可是非洲人吶
I can make fire. I'm from Africa.
All right, we got nothin'.
算了  一點結果都沒有
一定會很有樂趣的
We'll make it fun.
帶我離開這座島
Oh, get me of ff othis island!
誰都不會來救我們
I don't think anybody's coming.
情況可能會更糟
It could be worse.
我們至少還有彼此
At least we have each other.
麻煩給Taylor Swift換裝
Taylor Swift into next outfit, please.
Oh, my God!
天吶
為下一環節做準備
All right, prep next section!
準備下一環節
Prep next section!
他們去樓下找Cara了
Cara, they're looking for downstairs--
they're fixing her little outfit--
還在弄她的服裝
還有Jourdan沒找著人
and Jourdan-- those are the only ones I haven't seen.
廣告過後  "巴黎之夜"即將登場
After the break, spend a night with us in Paris.
Only CBS.
廣告過後  "巴黎之夜"即將登場
精彩盡在CBS
Only CBS.
天吶
Oh, my God!
我們以試衣模特為標準
MONICA MITRO: The looks model is the model that we use
制訂走秀服裝
to try on the fashion show outfits.
許多試衣模特都成為了維密巨星
Looks models become big Victoria's Secret stars.
包括Ale  Lindsay和Candice
We've had Ale, Lindansay d Candice.
我可以試穿所有服裝
I got to try every single outfit.
試戴首飾和羽毛
Trying on jewelry and feathers...
服裝的靈感令人驚喜
I was blown away by the ideas.
你們居然還有新點子
I can't believe you guys still have ideas left.
?Baby, in our wildest moment?..
This feels good. I like it.
這套不錯  我喜歡
?We could be the greatest, baby, in our wildest moment
?We could be the greatest, baby, in our wildest mom秂nt
試衣模特不好當
Being a looks model is actually a very difficult job,
你就像個衣架子
because you're a n humamannequin,
穿著半成品
and you're being picked and poked,
and they're literally making the outfit on you.
任憑設計師裁剪  等他們完成服裝
嗨  Barbara
Hey, Barbara.
Barbara Fialho是我們這幾年的
Barbara Fialho, who's been the looks model
試衣模特
for the past couple of years,
she is so enthusiastic about everything.
她對一切充滿了熱情
She inspires us,
她鼓舞了我們
讓大家工作都非常愉快
and she really gets the whole team in a great mood.
團隊裡能有Barbara這樣的人
It's so important for us to have
是非常重要的
someone like Barbara on the team.
這份工作棒極了
It's such an amazing job to have.
That's me. Oh, yeah.
這是我呀
去年是我的首秀  是個非常棒的經歷
The special last year was amazing.
在那之後  我的生活改變了許多
Since the last show, so much has changed.
我拿到了第一份化妝廣告
I did my first major cosmetic campaign.
參與了紀梵希的宣傳活動
I've done a lot of work for ncGivehy.
我的模特生涯更上了一層樓
Everything has come to a different level.
-我們為你選了一套服裝  -真的嗎
We chose an outfit for you. You did?
We think you're going to like it.
你一定會喜歡
Oh, my God!
天吶
Oh, my God.
我一開始就看上了這個
This is my favorite one, from the beginning.
你應得的
You deserve it, you deserve it. Oh...
旅途繼續
The journey continues.
再見
Bye.
Adriana準備  音樂五號
Stand by, Adriana. Music, track five!
投影和燈柱準備好
Projections Y-55, lampposts in at two!
Adriana在穿翅膀
Adriana's getting her wings on.
她從舞台左側進場
She'll be stage left.
Adriana  還有20秒進場
20 seconds, Adriana.
MILEY CYRUS: ?Oh, you broke my heart
?I told you
?I was weak for love
?But then you went around
?And did what you wanted to do ?
?And now I'm crying ?
?Crying
?Ooh, it seemed like everything was going fine ?
?I found love that I thought was gonna last ?
?Then I accidentally saw a few things in your cell ?
?I even LOL'd ?
?Man, I should've known ?
?Why, why you do what you do?
?You, you might as well just tell the honest truth ?
?See, I'm not really down with this ?
?This ain't no texting ?
?No, I got no biz, but it is what it is ?
?I don't really have much to say ?
?I was over it
?The second that I saw her name ?
?I got two, two
?Two letters for you
?One of them's whoo! And the other one's ?
?'Cause what you got to do is go get yourself a clue ?
?Only two, two, two
?Letters to choose
?One of them's whoo! And the other one's ?
?SMH, I'm pressing send on you ?
?Could've been this, couldn't been that ?
?We done been there, we done been back ?
?You ain't with it, could've said that ?
?Why you trippin', let me hear that ?
?I ain't trying to argue all morning ?
?I do it all for you
?You know you're my right eye ?
?Baby, let me show you
?Oh, I know what's been going on ?
?Don't even try to act like Mr. Super Nonchalant ?
?What makes you think I'll stick around ?
?I'm not as stupid as you sound, and you ?
?Sound really dumb right now
?From A to zed
?Ooh, ah
?I got a lot of nasty things
?Blowing up in my head
?But none of them are worth my time ?
?You're not even worth this rhyme ?
?And I don't, I don't ?
?Give a flying
?I don't really have much to say ?
?I was over it the second that I ?
?Saw her name
?I got two
?Two, two letters ?For you
?One of them's whoo! ?
?And the other one's ?
?'Cause what you got to do is go get yourself a clue ?
?Only two, two, two
?Letters to choose
?One of them's whoo! And the other one's ?
?Smh
?I'm pressing send on you ?
?Ooh, ooh, two letters for you ?
?Yeah ?Letters for you ?
?What you trippin' on, huh? ?
?Girl, you know you're wrong, huh ?
?Don't let these girls drive you crazy ?
?I don't really have much to say ?
?I was over it the second that I saw her name ?
?I got two, ooh, ooh, letters for you ?
?One of them's whoo! And the other one's ?
?'Cause what you gotta do is go get yourself a clue ?
?Only two, two, two, letters to choose ?
?One of them's ?
?And the other one's ?
?SMH, I'm pressing send on you ?
?I got two, two, two letters for you... ?
停止排放乾冰
And stop atmosphere now, please.
Stop atmosphere now.
Clyde  倒數60秒  撤下巴黎街燈
Clyde, cue 60-- the Parisian lamp post out.
?'Cause what you gotta do ?
?Is go get yourself a clue
?Only two, two, two, two...
?I'm pressing send on you. ?
今年的假日廣告是在巴黎拍的
This year, we shot the holiday commercial in Paris.
開拍
And action!
猶如夢境一般
It felt like a dream.
妙不可言
It was awesome.
我們決定在夜間拍攝
We decided to shooatt night.
午夜拍廣告  感覺有些挑逗
It feels a little naughty to shoot at midnight.
從全新的視角來拍攝
It's such a different way
內衣和天使們
to see the lingerie and see us.
我們睡了一白天  晚上八點才開始做造型
Wept sle all day, we'd go to hair and makeup at 8:00,
接著整晚都在拍廣告
and then shoot all through the night.
我們的生物鐘的確與眾不同
Our sleeping patterns were very interesting.
凌晨六點  我們還在香榭麗捨大街拍外景
00 a.M., we're shooting right in front of the ChaElmps-ysees.
當時我只穿著內衣
I'm just walking around in my wings
戴著翅膀走來走去  沒啥大不了的
in my bra and underwear, no big deal.
開拍
And action!
?I've been infected with restless ?
?Whispers and cheats...
巴黎的夜晚燈火絢爛
Paris is luminous.
它是光明之城
It's the City of Lights,
我們真的點亮了它的光芒
and we lit it up, literally.
維密公司花下重金
Victoria's Secret paid
讓埃菲爾鐵塔整晚閃爍
to keep the Eiffel Tower lit all night.
難以置信的美麗  特別和浪漫
It was unbelievably beautiful and special and romantic.
?Thanit mafested...
我當時真是凍得要命
It was finreezldg co.
天上還下著雪
It was practically snowing.
要是讓我受凍
Put me in a cold situation,
我就會不開心
and I'm not a happy girl.
這次的拍攝場面特別宏大
It's such a massive production.
拍了許多動人心魄的美麗場景
Beautiful, epic scenes.
是展現演技的好機會
It's an opportu tnityo perform.
為了展現性感  我通常會做這樣的表情
To turn seI xy, usually will do one of these.
這是搞怪版Behati
This is goofy Behati, um,
有點二的Behati
being sther supidelf.
這是性感版Candice
Ths is isexy Candice.
這才叫性感
And this is sexy.
有何貴幹
What?
大概有一千多位娛記
There was, like, a thousand paparazzi
想要拍到我們的照片
trying to get pictures of us...
但廣告拍攝依舊順利
But we got the shot.
沒什麼能阻擋維密假日廣告
Nothing can stop a VS holiday commercial.
Lais非常出色
Lais is simply amazing.
她是我認識的最甜美
She's the sweetest,
最溫柔  最美麗的姑娘
most gentle, beautiful thing I've ever seen.
我從沒在天橋上摔倒過
I've never fallen on the runway.
但世事無常  一旦發生後果極其沉重
But it's, you know, it happens, and it's awful when it does.
參加這個秀是每個女孩的夢想
To be in this show is a dream for every girl.
我十分重視它
It's a big deal.
去年在綵排的時候
Last year, I got there to do the rehearsal.
不知道怎麼回事
Then, I don't know how it happened.
我突然摔倒了
I just fell down.
我覺得我的腳踝斷了
I thought I broke my ankle.
恐懼感會一直縈繞在你腦海中
It's always in the back of your mind.
這件事真的特別可怕
It's a scary thing.
在綵排中扭傷腳踝
At the rehearsal,
然後無法參加走秀
hurt your foot, and you can't do the show?
這事太讓人傷心了
It was a very sad moment.
好了
Okay.
大家都嚇壞了
Everybody was freaking out
因為他們說
because they said it looked like
看上去很嚴重
her foot literally broke,
她的腳踝好像真的斷了
snapped from underneath her.
我當然特別沮喪
Of course, I was very upset.
我開始哭泣
You know, I start to cry.
當時的場面特別沉重
It was pretty heavy.
第二天  我醒來
And the next day, I woke up,
試著站起來
and then, I tried to put my feet on the ground.
還是不行
No.
沒法走路
No way to walk.
我不得不
I had to go out there
穿起她的裝扮  替她走秀
and walk the show in her look.
那感覺太糟糕了
It felt really horrible.
穿著她的裝扮太難受了
I felt so bad putting that outfit on,
因為那本是她的  不該由我去展現
'cause it wasn't mine, I wasn't supposed to have it.
今年  我做了更充足的準備
This year, I'm more than prepared for this show.
Lais  出來讓我們看看吧
Okay, Lais, can we see your outfit?
辣妹喲
Wow! It is hot!
試衣的時候
In the fitting,
我告訴他們  如果我又摔倒
I told them, if I fall again,
我一定會揮著翅膀飛起來
of course I'm gonna use my wings to fly.
因為去年你出了意外  所以今年
Because of what happened to you last year, we wanted you to know
我們希望你來走這個單元的開場
that we're going to have you open the section of the show
叫作"天堂飛鳥"
which is called "Birds of Paradise."
感謝你
: Thank you. Thank you. Thank you...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
今晚  我無比興奮和快樂
Tonight, I'm more than excited, happy.
也很緊張
Nervous.
我希望Lais今年
I want for Lais, this year,
能走一場最美妙的秀
to have the most incredible show,
穿最熱辣的衣服
to have the most incredible outfit,
希望一切都如她所願
to have whatever she wants.
我們都會在她身後支持她
We're all gonna be behind her this year, and be, like,
為她歡呼
"Yeah!"
我一定會在後台支持她
I will definitely find Lais backstage.
祝她享受最美時刻
I want her to just have the best time.
上吧
Kill it.
Fall Out Boy登台吧
MAN : Preset Fall Out Boy, go!
? Fall Out Boy – "The Phoenix" ?
?Put on your war paint
?You are a brick tied to me that's dragging me down ?
?Strike a match and I'll burn you to the ground
姑娘  上吧
Go, baby, go!
?Strike a match and I'll burn you to the ground
?We are the jack-o'-lanterns in July ?
?Setting fire to the sky
?Here it comes this rising tide c, soome on ?
?Put on your war paint
?Cross walks and crossed hearts and hope-to-dies ?
?Silver clouds with gliray ning ?
?So we can take the world back from a heart attack ?
?One maniac at a time we will take it back ?
?Time crawls on
?When you're waiting for the song to start ?
?Dance alone to the beat of your heart ?
?Hey, young blood, doesn't it feel ?
?Like our time is running out? ?
?I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
?Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
?It's our vintage misery ?
?No, I think it looked a little better on me ?
?I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
?Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
?Bring home the boys and scrap, scrap methtal e tanks ?
?Get hitched, make a career out of robbing banks ?
?Because the world is just a teller ?
?And we are wearing black masks ?
?"You broke our spirit" Says the note we pass ?
?Take the world back from a heart attack ?
?One maniac at a time, we'll take it back ?
?Time crawls on
?When you're waiting for the song to start ?
?Dance alone to the beat of your heart ?
?Hey, young blood, doesn't it feel ?
?Like our time is running out? ?
?I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
?Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
?It's our vintage misery ?
?No, I think it looked a little better on me ?
?I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
?Then I'll raise you like a phoenix ?
?The war is won before it's begun ?
維密秀  歡呼聲在哪裡
Victoria Secret, make some noise!
?The war is won before it's begun ?
維密秀  歡呼聲在哪裡
Victoria Secret, make some noise!
?Release the doves, surrender love ?
?The war is won before it's begun ?
?Wave the white flag! Wave the white flag! ?
?Before it's begun ?
?Release the dove ?Wave the white flag! Wave the white flag! ?
?Surrender love ?Wave the white flag! Wave the white flag! ?
?The war is won before it's begun ?
?Rseelea d theoves ?Wave the white f lag!?
?Wave the white flag! ? ?Surrender love
?Hey, young blood
?Doesn't it feel like our time is running out? ?
?I'm gonna change you like a remix ?
?Then I'll raise you like a phoenix. ?
注意翅膀  小心點兒
Okay, watch the wings. Watch the wings.
這是我正常的樣子
This is my natural look.
這是我性感的樣子
And this... is my sexy look.
等等  我都不知道我性感是什麼樣
Oh, wait-- I don't know what my sexy look is!
矮油  我看起來性感嗎
Oh, gosh, do I look sexy?
你確定嗎
Are you sure about that?
關鍵在頭髮
It's all about the hair.
走秀風來一個
Now on to the runway.
好樣的
There we go.
真的好好笑
: It's just too funny.
這才是我性感的樣子
This is my sexy look.
下節精彩
Still to come...
Taylor Swift和Neon Jungle登場
Taylor Swift and Neon Jungle.
雙重驚喜哦
That's double trouble.
精彩盡在CBS
Only CBS.
?Let's go ?
?I wanna go around the world
?And party with the girls
? ' Le's go ?
nd?A when I get there, wh gen Iet there ?
?When I'm there I wanna go-o-o ?
?Ina wan go crazy
?I wanna go
?I wanna go crazy
?That's where I wanna go ?
?I wanna go cra-cra-cra-cra- cra-cra-crazy-zy-zy-zy-zy ?
?We like to sleep all day...
維密時尚內衣秀
加入維密話題
#vsfashionshow.
維密時尚內衣秀
?This is how we like to live our life ?
?Hands up!
今晚這場秀裡的
All of the models
所有模特
that are in the show tonight
其實都是社交媒體上的明星
are literally the rock stars of social media.
發些東西到網上很好啊
It's a great way to get stuff out there.
?Let's go! ?
我最開始接觸的是Twitter
I started with Twitter.
我從那裡得到所有的消息
That's where I get all of my news.
沒有Instagram沒法活啊
I would die without Instagram.
我覺得Facebook很棒
Facebook, I think, is great.
誰是爆照狂人
Who's the most fearless poster?
Cara
Cara.
不好意思
Cara Delevingne. Sorry.
她在社交媒體上很有影響力
She's remarkably powerful in social media.
這很好啊
That's a good point, though, yeah.
網絡平台很自由
There's so much freedom.
沒有任何限制  暢所欲言
There is no boundaries; you can say whatever you want.
她特別大膽
She is fearless.
我沒考慮太多  想做什麼就做什麼
I don't think about it, I just do it.
我喜歡她這態度
I like her attitude about that.
她們的粉絲多得嚇人
It's crazy how many followers they have.
我在Instagram上有290萬粉絲
2.9 million people follow me on Instagram.
總共得有上千萬的粉絲
Collectively, it's in the tens of millions.
我每隔三四分鐘
LILY: I pick up my phone
就會拿起手機看看
at least every three to four minutes.
每次打開手機  都會看到新的東西
Every time you pick it up, there's something else to look at.
我發的大多都關於
I like to post a balance
家庭  工作和慈善的東西
between family, work, and charity.
鼓舞人心的名人名言
Inspiring quotes.
積極向上的消息
Positive messages.
有時我發了不該發的照片
Sometimes I post photos I shouldn't.
我所擁有的一切
In one second, I could
就可能立刻毀於一旦
screw up everything I have.
就好像按了一個巨大的紅色按鈕
It's like the big red button.
一切瞬間爆炸
And everything explodes.
小心哦
Be careful.
悔推  你不能發任何讓你後悔的東西
tweegret-- You shouldn't tweegret anything.
我想我以前刪過一些東西
I feel like I've deleted something before,
但我不記得是什麼了
but I can't remember what it is.
-刪除  -我還沒碰到情況糟糕到
Delete. I haven't had, like, a shocking moment
我得找我的經紀人  讓他"快刪掉"
that I had to get... My agency is like, "Get that off!"
Instagram蒙羞
instashame.
生命苦短  沒空在Instagram上蒙羞
Life is too short for instashame.
隨便去谷歌搜一搜
You can just go on Google
很容易就搜到我的屁股了
and see my butt anyway.
太瘋狂了
That's crazy.
咱們現在應該幹點壞事兒
We should do something bad right now.
-我知道  有"助"形象  -沒錯
I know, it'd be great for our image. Yeah.
這個品牌在世界上如此聞名
One of the reasons the brand is so
也得益於她們那些社交活動
well-known worldwide is because of their social activity.
這也是工作的一部分
It's part of the job.
是嗎
Is it?
維密時尚內衣秀
vsfashionshow.
準備  所有粉紅女郎
MAN : Okay, stand by, all Pink girls.
請所有粉紅模特到前台
Please, can I have all Pink models onstage now?
這是我第一次走台
It's my first time walking,
穿上這身美麗的衣服還有翅膀
and I got this amazing outfit with wings.
真是無比榮幸
I mean, it's such an honor.
其他人為我第一次表演而緊張
Makes me nervous that other people are nervous for me
這也讓我很緊張
for being here for the first time.
我沒辦法停止  我臉上
I can't take my-- this, like, stupid smile
這傻乎乎的笑  我都笑了好幾周了
that's on my face-- it's been there for, like, weeks.
Neon Jungle請到開場位置  馬上
Neon Jungle to opening positions, please-- now.
女士們先生們  掌聲歡迎
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome to America
無與倫比的Neon Jungle
the incredible Neon Jungle.
Trouble
?I don't look for troub le,but trouble looks for me ?
?And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
?They say, "Here comes a hurricane ?
?Trouble is her middle name"
?But I don't look for trouble, yeah, tre oubllooks for me ?
? Heyhey
?I don't look for trouble ?
?But trouble looks for me
?And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
?They say, "Here comes a hurricane ?
?Trouble is her middle name"
?But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
?Hey, hey
?I just want to live a quiet life ?
?I'll make an excellent wife ?
?Man, I swear I really try
?But some boys-- they just can't eat it whole ?
?Trouble is my name, k younow
?Trouble is my name, you know ?
?I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
?And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
?They say, "Here comes a hurricane ?
?Trouble is her middle name"
?But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
?Hey, hey
?Hey
?I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
?And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
?They say that girl got so many sides ?
?Uh, I'm a Gemini ?
?But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
?Hey, hey
?Hey
?Lights up, let's have a toke ?
?Pour more whiskey in my Coke
?Never been one of the herd
?Flippin' everyone the bird ?
?People say that I am heartless ?
?I've just learned to use my heart less ?
?I go hard 'cause I'm the hardest ?
?And we ain't even started yet ?
?Hey
?Hey, hey
?Trouble
?I don't look for trouble, but trouble looks for me ?
?And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
?They say, "Here comes a hurricane ?
?Trouble is her middle name"
?But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
?Hey, hey, I don't look for trouble ?
?But trouble looks for me
?And it's been waiting around corners since I was 17 ?
?They say, "Here comes a hurricane ?
?Trouble is her middle name"
?But I don't look for trouble, yeah, trouble looks for me ?
?Hey, hey
?Trouble.
謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝大家
Taylor來表演啦
Taylor's in the show.
好激動
Excitement.
她才華橫溢
She's amazingly talented
還那麼美麗
and so gorgeous.
Taylor是典型的美國女孩
Taylor is this all-American girl,
她就像美國夢一樣
she's like the American Dream,
我想我們一定會玩得很開心的
and I think we're gonna have a lot of fun.
太棒了
Okay, awesome.
-我們已經是好多年的朋友  -閨蜜
We've been friends for years. Besties.
看到她在工作的同時
And getting to see her do her job
我也在工作
at the same time as I'm doing my job...
-我知道  -不可思議啊
I know. ...it's crazy.
那首《Trouble》
Trouble.
《Trouble》
BOTH : Trouble.
廣告之後  我的閨蜜Taylor Swift即將登台
After the break, my girl Taylor Swift.
要如何成為一位天使呢
What does it t aketo be an Angel?
竭盡全力
Everything you've got.
即使那樣也還是不夠
An end evt' than's out en
?I want your body, everybody wants your body ?
?So let's jack, let's jack... ?
這需要集中精力
ADRIANA: It takes focus,
需要下定決心  需要付出耐力
it takes commitment, and it takes endurance.
但缺乏力量的美是空洞的
But beauty is nothing without strength.
這些姑娘的訓練堪比專業運動員
These girls train like professionahll atetes
她們為了夢想的身材而努力鍛煉
and they really work for the bodies that they want.
Michael讓我像拳手一樣訓練
Michael trains me like a fighter.
而且這場戰鬥永無止境
And the figh t ve netur acally ends.
我為走秀而鍛煉
I work out for the runway, but mostly I work out for life.
但更多時候是在為自己的人生而鍛煉
Adriana有真本事
Adrian ta ishe real deal.
我為她制定的體能訓練十分瘋狂
' Ita's mental I ast is physical for her.
她的勁頭勢不可擋
And she's unstoppable.
?Jack, jacack, jk, jack
?Jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack, jack... ?
我喜歡大汗淋漓
I like to sweat.
?Everybody wants your body...
我喜歡運動不止
I like to keep moving.
當我愛上某種東西  我會全情投入
When I love something, I commit.
你跟Adriana一起走
WOMAN : You're walking with Adriana.
候場了  Adriana
Stand by, Adriana.
Taylor來了  候場
Taylor's entrance. Stand by.
Behati到位
Behati's right here.
她到了  她到了
She's made it, she's made it.
Taylor就位
We have Taylor!
請她上台  有請Taylor Swift
Send her. Send Taylor Swift.
女士們先生們  請熱烈歡迎
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome back
獨一無二的Taylor Swift
the one and onayly Tlor Swift.
?Once upon a time, a few mistakes ago ?
?I was in your sights, you got me alone ?
?You found me, you found me
?You found me-ee-ee-ee-ee
?I guess you didn't care ?
?And I guess I liked that
?And when I fell hard, you took a step back ?
?Without me, without me
?Without me-ee-ee-ee-ee-ee
?And he's long gone ?
?When he's next to me ?
?And I realize
?The blame is on me
?'Cause I knew you were trouble ?
?When you walked in
?So shame on me now
?Flew me to places I never been ?
?Till you put me down, oh
?I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
?Shame on me now
?Flew me to places I never been ?
?Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground ?
?Oh, oh
?Trouble, trouble, trouble
?No apologies
?He'll never see you cry ?
?Pretends he doesn't know that he's the reason why ?
?You're drowning, you're drowning ?
?You're drown-ee-ee-ee-ee-ing ? 916 00:54: 00:54:48,818
?Now, I heard you moved on from whispers on the street ?
?A new notch in your belt is all I'll ever be ?
?Now I see
?Now I see, now I see ee-ee-ee-ee
?He was long gone
?When he met me
?And I realize
?The joke is on me
?Yeah!
?I knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
?So shame on me now,
flew me to places i never been
?Till you put me down, oh, I knew you were ?
?Trouble when you walked in
?So shame on me now
?Flew me to places I never been ?
?Now I'm lying on the cold hard ground ?
?Oh, oh
?Trouble, trouble, trouble
?Trouble, trouble ?Trouble,
and the saddest fear ?
?Comes creeping in
?That you never loved me
?Or her or anyone
?Or anything
?Yeah...
?I knew you were trouble When you walked in ?Yeah...
?So shame on me now ?
?Flew me to places I never been ?
?Never been till you put me down, oh ?
?Knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
?So shame on me now
?Flew me to places ?I never been
?Now I'm lying ?
?On the cold hard ground, oh ?Oh
?Trouble, trouble, trouble
?Oh, oh
?Trouble, trouble ? ?Trouble, ah
?Knew you were ?
?Trouble when you walked in
?Trouble, trouble, trouble
?Knew you were trouble when you walked in ?
?Trouble, trouble, trouble.
進第七首音樂  二  一  走
MAN : Now music track seven in two, one-- go!
上吧  寶貝兒們  上上上
Go, babes. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
來來來
Come on, come on.
太讚了  贊贊贊
Well done, well done.
?The applause, applause, applause ?
?Give me that thing that I love ?
?I'll turn the lights on ?
?Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch ?
?Give me that thing that I love ?
?I'll turn the lights on ?
?Put your hands up, make 'em touch ?
?Make it real loud...
?A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E ?Make it real loud
?Put your hands up, make 'em touch ?
?Make it real loud...
?A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E ?Make it real loud
?Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch ?
?Put your hands up, make ' 'emouch, touch ?
?A-p-p-l-a-u-s-e
?Make it real loud
?Put your hands up, make 'em toutoch, uch ?
?A-P-P-L-A-U-S-E ?Make it real loud
?Put your hands up, make 'em touch, touch ?
?I live for the applause
?Applause, applause
?I live for the applause-plause ?
?Live for the applause-plause... ?
2013年走秀圓滿落幕
Okay, class of 2013.
現在要在後台拍個照
So, we're shooting something backstage about now.
大家要拍個合影
They're fielding a photograph.
任務很艱巨  你們要拍個集體大合影
RUSSELL JAMES: thNow e hard part.
You have to have a photo all together.
2013年大合影
The 2013 shot.
你們想要Taylor是吧
Yontu wa Taylor.
對哦  誰能抗拒得了Taylor Swift呢
Yes. Who can say no to Taylor Swift?
大家靠近一點
Now, get in close together.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
謝謝
JAMES: Thank you.
太棒了  謝謝  收工咯
Fantastic. Thank you. Thats 'a wrap.